withtank.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy policy / About / Knowledge Base - Tank Support

thisarmy respects the privacy of each Customer. thisarmy has established this Privacy Policy to explain how Data is collected by thisarmy, and how this Data is used and disclosed. thisarmy takes the protection of Personal Information very seriously. thisarmy may process (for example, collect, use or disclose) Personal Information only as described in this Privacy Policy.

Version number: 1.0

## Definitions and Interpretations

**Definitions.** For purposes of the Privacy Policy:

‘ _Data_ ’ means any data (including Personal Information) provided to thisarmy by a Customer;

‘ _Personal Information_ ’ means any Data or information about an identifiable Customer, including an email address.

**Interpretation.** Words defined or assigned a meaning in the Agreement will have that meaning in this Privacy Policy, unless the context clearly indicates otherwise.

## Collection

**Collection on registration.** Once a Customer registers with thisarmy, a Customer is not anonymous to thisarmy. When registering, each Customer provides Data, which includes an ID, a password, and an email address. To combat online fraud, thisarmy may also record the IP address of a Customer when adding Data. In addition, a Customer may provide necessary Personal Information to process a credit card payment, including a billing address.

**Decline to share.** A Customer can decline to share Personal Information with thisarmy by not registering with thisarmy.

**Children.** thisarmy does not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.

**Collection from browser.** thisarmy automatically receives and records information on thisarmy’s server logs from the browser of a Customer, including an IP address, cookie information, and the page requested. Each Customer should be aware that other web sites visited before entering the web site might place Personal Information within a URL of a Customer during a visit to it, and thisarmy has no control over such web sites. Accordingly, a subsequent web site that collects URL information may log some Personal Information.

## Use

**Messages and updates.** thisarmy may send to a Customer administrative messages and email updates regarding its account, the web site, or its Goods or Services. In some cases, thisarmy may also send a Customer primarily promotional messages. A Customer can choose to opt-out of promotional messages.

**Cookies.** Personal Information may be used to improve the web site. thisarmy may use cookies to save the IDs and session validators of a Customer on its browsers and hard drives, and may use cookies to provide a tailored web site. IP addresses also help thisarmy to diagnose problems with and to administer the web site.

**Targeted content.** While a Customer is logged into the web site, thisarmy may display targeted adverts and other relevant information based on the Data. In a completely automated process, computers process the Data and match it to adverts or related information. Natural persons do not read Data to target adverts or other information without consent. thisarmy never shares Personal Information with any advertiser, unless a Customer specifically asks thisarmy to do so. Advertisers receive a record of the total number of impressions and clicks for each advert. They do not receive any Personal Information. If a Customer clicks on an advert, thisarmy may send a referringURL to the advertiser’s site identifying that a Customer is visiting from the web site. thisarmy does not send Personal Information to advertisers with the referring URL. Once a Customer is on the advertiser’s site however, the advertiser may collect Personal Information.

## Disclosure

**No selling.** thisarmy will not sell, share, or distribute Personal Information. No Personal Information may be disclosed to anyone except as provided in this Privacy Policy.

**Marketing purposes.** thisarmy may disclose aggregate statistics (information about the customer population in general terms) about the Data to advertisers or business partners for marketing purposes.

**Third party supplier or agents.** thisarmy may need to provide Data to a third party supplier to supply or provide specific Goods or Services to a Customer (such as hosting services, support services, shipping services, or payment processing). Each third party supplier is required to only disclose or use the Data to supply or provide the specific Goods or Services requested.

**Law enforcement.** thisarmy may disclose Data if required: by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order by law; to protect the safety of any individual or the general public; to prevent violation of the Agreement, or the rights of thisarmy or any third party. An IP address may be disclosed to a third party: if the law or a legal process requires it; to protect the rights or property of thisarmy, a Customer, or the general public.

**Affiliates.** thisarmy may share Data with an Affiliate, in which case thisarmy will seek to require the Affiliates to honour this Privacy Policy.

**Change of ownership.** If thisarmy undergoes a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, thisarmy may assign its rights to the Data it processes to a successor, purchaser, or separate entity. thisarmy will notify each Customer of the transfer and the Customer may choose to modify its Personal Data at that time. If a Customer is concerned about its Data migrating to a new owner, the User may deactivate or delete its account.

**Employees.** thisarmy may need to disclose Data to its employees that require the Data to do their jobs.

**Abuse.** thisarmy may disclose Data to designated third parties to resolve or investigate abuse complaints. thisarmy may release Data to assist in attempting to block an abusive Customer or complain to its Internet Service Provider of an abusive Customer.

## Security of data

thisarmy uses some of the most advanced security measures to protect the Data under its control. All Data is safe, secure, and available only to the Customer and those to whom Customer has granted permissions. In addition, the web site is hosted in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced security measures to prevent interference or access from outside intruders.

## Username and password

During the registration process, thisarmy will provide Customer with a username and password. It is the responsibility of each Customer to maintain the confidentiality and security of their password.

## Updating or removing

A Customer may choose to correct or update the Data they have submitted to thisarmy, by going to their account. To remove any Data from the active database of thisarmy, a User may deactivate or delete their account. Even if a Customer updates or removes their Data from thisarmy’s live database, Data may be retained in thisarmy’s backup files and archives.

## Unauthorised use

Any unauthorised use of thisarmy information systems is a violation of the Agreement and certain laws, including the section 86 of the ECT Act. Such violations may subject the person to civil and criminal penalties.

## Intercept and monitor

thisarmy may intercept, monitor, block, filter, read, delete, and disclose any communication over its information system.

## Limitation

thisarmy is not responsible for, gives no warranties, nor makes any representations in respect of the privacy policies or practices of linked or any third party web sites.

## International customers

thisarmy may transmit or transfer Personal Information outside the resident jurisdiction of the Customer and therefore across borders. Personal Information may be stored on servers located in the United States where laws protecting Personal Information may not be as stringent as the laws in the jurisdiction of the Customer. Personal Information may be processed by thisarmy in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent.

## Enquiries

If anyone has any questions or concerns arising from this Privacy Policy or the way in which thisarmy handles Personal Information, please contact support@withtank.com.
